H. T. Premachandra

I am a self-motivated individual with a proven track record as a Management Assistant with 04 years of experience. I put my heart into what I do and will always strive to deliver my best possible. I'm loyal and I am willing to go the extra mile. I could work in any circumstance either as a part of a team or with minimal supervision.



tharindulivingcl@gmail.com



071 26 46 495



279/a, Gedabaduwa Road, Kindelpitiya, Welmilla, Bandaragama



06 May, 1993

SKILLS & SPECIALTIES

Computer Applications
Proficiency (MS windows,
office, outlook, teams etc.)

Strong Language & Communications Skills

Hardworking and Self Motivated

Multi Tasker

Quick Learner

LANGUAGES

English

Full professional proficiency

Sinhala

Native/Bilingual proficiency

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Built a personal portfolio/webpage to display my profile online 2019

https://tharindu01.github.io/tharindu

WORK EXPERIENCE

Management Assistant

Telecommunications Regulatory Commission of Sri Lanka 06/2019 to present (4+ years)

Sales Consultant

Ceylinco Life Insurance Company Ltd 07/2014 - 03/2015

EDUCATION

Diploma in English

Aquinas College of Higher Studies 2015 - 2016

General Certificate of Education (Advanced Level)

Bandaragama National School

Commerce Stream 2012

English - A • Business Studies
Economics - B • Accounting

- B

- C

General Certificate of Education (Ordinary Level)

Bandaragama National School 2009

English - A **Buddhism** - A Health & Phy. Studies Mathematics - B - A - C Citizenship Education - B History -S Sinhala - C Science -S English Literature

OTHER INFORMATION

Bachelor of Information Technology

University of Colombo – (External) 2016-2018 Unfinished